<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Quick Temps</string>
    <string name="section_format">Hello World from section: %1$d</string>
    <string name="hourly">24 Hour</string>
    <string name="daily">Daily</string>
    <string name="ok">OK</string>
    <string name="permission_required_reason">Unable to get permission to access your location.\nQuick Temps needs access to your location in order to work correctly. \nPlease allow access before continuing.</string>
    <string name="settings_required_reason">Access to location services is required for the application to work properly. Please enable location services to continue.</string>
    <string name="exit">Exit</string>
    <string name="try_again">TRY AGAIN</string>
    <string name="location_settings_failure_message">Quick Temps failed to acquire location services. Location services are a required for the application to work properly. Please enable them and try again.</string>
    <string name="requires_gps_failure_reason">Quick Temps requires Google Play Services to run successfully. In particular it needs location services. Please make sure these services are installed and enabled on your device then try again.</string>
    <string name="loading_data">Retrieving weather information and forecasts from OpenWeatherMap.org</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="git_hub">GitHub</string>
    <string name="linked_in">Linked In</string>
    <string name="open_weather_map">OpenWeatherMap.org</string>
    <string name="about_description_connecting">Connecting OpenWeatherMap.org weather services with your device to give you the latest local weather and forecast information.</string>
    <string name="about_description_osm">OpenWeatherMap supplies wide range of weather data including current weather, forecast, precipitations, wind, clouds, data from weather stations, lots of maps, analytics and many others. They have their own model of weather calculation that involves global meteorological broadcast data, custom WRF calculation for regions and real-time data from more than 40,000 weather stations.</string>
    <string name="about_description_mck">This application was developed by Michael King and is available free of charge. The code is available on GitHub and licensed under Apache 2.0</string>
    <string name="about_description_thank_you">Thank you for downloading and using this application.</string>
    <string name="fahrenheit">Fahrenheit</string>
    <string name="celsius">Celsius</string>
    <string name="imperial">Imperial</string>
    <string name="metric">Metric</string>
    <string name="humidy">Humidy</string>
    <string name="cloudiness">Cloudiness</string>
    <string name="wind">Wind</string>
    <string name="icon">icon</string>
    <string name="time">TIME</string>
    <string name="generated">generated</string>
    <string name="weather_data_error_message">Unfortunately there has been an error connecting to OpenWeatherMaps.org would you like to try again?</string>

</resources>
